telechargement.fr 2017-12-28

# Legal notice & Privacy – Nexway

### LEGAL NOTICE & PRIVACY

NEXWAY (“NEXWAY” or “we”) offers visitors and users access to this website based on (and in reliance on) your acceptance of the following terms. NEXWAY hereby grants to you a nontransferable, nonexclusive license to access, download and use this website solely for your internal use. We may in our sole discretion add, delete, or change some or all the services included within the website at any time or terminate this license. All materials, including but not limited to the configurations, displays, screens, and all information appearing on or displayed in connection with or contained by NEXWAY on this website are protected under applicable laws.  
NEXWAY owns, reserves and retains all proprietary rights, including copyrights, to this website and its materials. The trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos and other indication of origin, including but not limited to, NEXWAY’s domain name, displayed on this website are registered and unregistered trademarks of NEXWAY or a third party who has granted NEXWAY a right to use them in this site. Nothing contained herein should be construed as granting the browser or user any license or right to use any trademark displayed on the site without the written permission of NEXWAY or such third party. NEXWAY and/or third-party content providers remain the owners of the information on this website, and that User does not acquire any of those ownership rights by printing or downloading any of the information or making use of the functionalities of the website.  
For information concerning our use of information relating to you and your use of our site see the Privacy Statement. The information contained on the website is for evaluative purposes only and is not intended to be relied upon by, or to create any warranty to, any visitor or any other person. Accordingly USE OF THE WEBSITE IS ENTIRELY AT USER’S OWN RISK IS “AS IS,” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND OR RESPONSIBILITY EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING (WITHOUT LIMITATION) ANY WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR OTHERWISE.  
French law will govern these conditions of use. The French Courts have the jurisdiction to judge any claim related to the use of this website.

**Legal Information:**

Website is published by: NEXWAY, S.A.S., Tour PB5 – 1 avenue du Général de Gaulle – 92074 Paris – La Défense CEDEX, France  
Head Office address: NEXWAY – Tour PB5 – 1 avenue du Général de Gaulle – 92074 Paris – La Défense CEDEX, France  
Greffe of NANTERRE  
SIRET: 44095385900046  
RCS Nanterre: B 440 953 859

Tel: +33 (0)1 55 17 31 55  
Hosting: Alionis, 30 rue Saint Lazare, 75009 Paris, France.

Share Capital of the company: 1.632.221 Euros

VAT Number: FR 33 440953859  
eMail contact : [srvc@nexway.com](mailto:srvc@nexway.com)

**Privacy Statement:**

The privacy and the security of your information are important to us. NEXWAY’s policy is to respect and protect the privacy of the users of this website. We will not willfully disclose individually identifiable information about our customers to any third party without first receiving that user’s permission.

**Collection of information**

NEXWAY only asks for specific types of personal information. In a few areas on our website, we may ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. Unless the requested information is required, it is completely optional for you to participate, but in accepting the terms and conditions of this website, you authorize us to collect them. We may ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, customer preference information, customer number, as well as other similar personal information that may be needed for registration. In agreement with the French law N° 2004-801 of August 6th, 2004, relevant to protection of people against treatment of personal data and modifying the “Informatique et Liberté n° 78-17 of January 6th,1978?, you can access to personal information and ask for modification by contacting the webmaster.

In agreement with the French law 2004-575 of June 21, 2004 for trust in the digital economy, the site also offers to Internet users who subscribe to it, a service called “email updates” to receive ongoing company updates from NEXWAY via email communications. All email communications offer a link to unsubscribe to the service.

**Use of information**

NEXWAY only uses your personal information for specific purposes. The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with NEXWAY. We may use your personal information to determine the demographics of our users and to distribute statistics and general marketplace information about NEXWAY. These demographics will always represent aggregate information and never identify a specific user. Also, we may disclose aggregated user information to describe our services and products to current and prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties and for other lawful purposes, including planning for and implementing advertising or promotional campaigns. Additionally, NEXWAY and its affiliates may utilize direct mailings to make direct product offers to you. You can opt-out of receiving further marketing from NEXWAY at any time.

**Disclosure of information**

NEXWAY will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent. Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) will not be given or sold to any outside organization. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of NEXWAY and its affiliated companies for the purpose of performing services for NEXWAY.

Internet commerce and security – NEXWAY is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called Secured Socket Layer (“SSL”) encryption. The SSL server that we utilize encrypts information before sending it to us.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. We strive to protect your personal information by implementing these security precautions, but we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. You do so at your own risk.

**Cookies**

New technologies are emerging on the Internet that help us deliver customized visitor experiences. At NEXWAY, we utilize “cookies” to help us provide you with a high quality experience. “Cookies” are text information files that your web browser places on your computer when you visit a website. Such cookies and other devices allow us to store and track information about you. Among other things, such devices allow us to be reminded of who you are and to access your account information, to measure the audience and usage of our pages, allow us to target advertisers and to track visitors to, and business conducted on, the website, and measure certain traffic patterns in order to customize the content, banner ads, promotions and other advertisements delivered to you. However, please be assured that advertisers that are not affiliated with NEXWAY will never have access to your individual account information. NEXWAY has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the NEXWAY website.

**Modification**

NEXWAY reserves the right to modify or supplement this Privacy Statement at any time. Because of this, you should read this Privacy Statement every time you access the NEXWAY website. All modifications or supplements to this Privacy Statement are effective when posted on the website.
